Thomas S. Power Papers
Thomas S. Power Papers
- Audiovisual material
  - Tapes
    - Washington Report of the Air, for April 29 - May 3, 1968; power_ts_0011; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 20)
      Tape 1, For April 29 - Dr. Judd - Domestic Violence Promoted by Reds; Tape 2, For April 30 - Dr. Judd interview with Edgar Ansel Mowrer - West Germany Looks Toward the East; Tape 3, For May 1 - Dr. Judd - Is It Peace on Hanoi’s Terms?; Tape 4, For May 2 - Dr. Judd interview with General Thomas S. Power - A Credible Nuclear Deterrent; Tape 5, For May 3 - Dr. Judd - Red Unrest in Poland. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for May 13 - May 17, 1968; power_ts_0012; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 20)
      Tape 1, For May 13 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Turmoil and trials inside Russia; Tape 2, For May 14 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd interview with Edward S. Butler - Communist Vietnam’s propaganda apparatus in the U.S.; Tape 3, For May 15 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - Cambodian sanctuary for the Reds; Tape 4, For May 16 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - India’s political shift to the Left; Tape 5, For May 17 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Olympic Games hypocrisy. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for May 20 - May 24, 1968; power_ts_0013; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 20)
      Tape 1, For May 20 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - New realism in the United Nations; Tape 2, For May 21 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd interview with Paul D. Bethel - Cuban subversion in Puerto Rico; Tape 3, For May 22 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd interview with Paul D. Bethel - Cuban subversion of U.S. Black Power movement; Tape 4, For May 23 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interview with Paul D. Bethel - How to resolve the Cuban threat; Tape 5, For May 24 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Anti-Communist nature of Red China turmoil. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for June 10 - June 14, 1968; power_ts_0014; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 20)
      Tape 1, For June 10 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - West’s policy toward satellites - No time for freedom; Tape 2, For June 11 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - French rapport with Communists and chaos, while Paris burns; Tape 3, For June 12 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd interview with W.K. Lambie - Sparks that ignite revolution; Tape 4, For June 13 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - Unrest in Brazil - From Communists to Clergy; Tape 5, For June 14 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - The extent of Mao’s desperation. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for June 17 - June 21, 1968; power_ts_0015; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 20)
      Tape 1, For June 17 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - U.S. Policy threatens our base in Pakistan; Tape 2, For June 18 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - Red China’s new rail penetration in Africa; Tape 3, For June 19 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - Future of our Spanish bases in jeopardy; Tape 4, For June 20 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interview with General Thomas S. Power - The correct role of the U.S. serviceman; Tape 5, For June 21 (Friday) - Dr. Judd interview with General Thomas S. Power - Effort to destroy the serviceman’s morale. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for July 1 - July 5, 1968; power_ts_0017; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 20)
      Tape 1, For July 1 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - American diplomacy operates on double standards; Tape 2, For July 2 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - Passport hypocrisy as practised by the British; Tape 3, For July 3 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd interviews Mr. Charles Wiley - Truth about the ARVN; Tape 4, For July 4 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - Communist China: In spite of the masses; Tape 5, For July 5 (Friday) - Dr. Judd interviews General T.S. Power - The true meaning of peace (as both sides see it). The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for July 8 - July 12, 1968; power_ts_0018; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 20)
      Tape 1, For July 8 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Violence in America: An assessment; Tape 2, For July 9 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd interviews Dr. Herminio Portell-Vila: New Red labor movement in Latin America; Tape 3, For July 10 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - Soviet power invades Czechoslovakia; Tape 4, For July 11 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interviews General T.S. Power - Defense research on campus; Tape 5, For July 12 (Friday) - Dr. Judd interviews with General T.S. Power: Young Americans - Our real source of strength. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for July 15 - July 19, 1968; power_ts_0019; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 20)
      Tape 1, For July 15 (Monday) - Dr. Judd talks about Al-Fattah: The Arab underground in Israel; Tape 2, For July 16 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - Cuban power: Threat to the United States in 1968; Tape 3, For July 17 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - The Consular Treaty: Merely a Communist shell game; Tape 4, For July 18 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - President Balaguer’s position in Dominican Republic; Tape 5, For July 19 (Friday) - Dr. Judd interviews Dr. Herminio Portell-Vila: How Panama is assisting the Communists. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for July 22 - July 26, 1968; power_ts_0020; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 20)
      Tape 1, For July 22 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - The Czech crisis: A repeat of Hungarian uprising?; Tape 2, For July 23 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - U.S. Forces in Far East unable to react in time to save "Pueblo" from capture; Tape 3, For July 24 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - South Korea’s needs for defense against aggression; Tape 4, For July 25 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interviews J.F. Lewis - Dominican Republic: Ready for another Communist take-over; Tape 5, For July 26 (Friday) - Dr. Judd interviews J.F. Lewis - Where anti-communist strength lies in Dominican Republic. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for July 29 - August 2, 1968; power_ts_0021; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 20)
      Tape 1, For July 29 (Monday) - Dr. Judd interview with Edgar Ansel Mowrer - West Germany and Nuclear non-proliferation; Tape 2, For July 30 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - Two Roman Catholic priests support Red terrorism; Tape 3, For July 31 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - Laos and Cambodia concerned about their survival; Tape 4, For August 1 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - The Diary of Che Guevara: How authentic is it?; Tape 5, For August 2 (Friday) - Dr. Judd interview with Edgar Ansel Mowrer - Possible West German agreement with Moscow. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for June 24 - June 28, 1968; power_ts_0016; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 20)
      Tape 1, For June 24 - Dr. Judd - Exposure of new Red threats to our security; Tape 2, For June 25 - Dr. Judd interview with Gen. Thomas S. Power - Potential contribution of Vietnam Vets; Tape 3, For June 26 - Dr. Judd - France’s Labor - Student coalition planned in Moscow; Tape 4, For June 27 - Dr. Judd - Red-led Trade Unions take more militant stance; Tape 5, For June 28 - Dr. Judd interview with Charles Wiley - Harmful reporting of Vietnam war. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for August 5 - August 9, 1968; power_ts_0022; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 20)
      Tape 1 For August 5 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - NORAD: The United States obsolete warning system; Tape 2 For August 6 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - U.S. decision to cut back on defenses weakens our bargaining position with Russia; Tape 3 For August 7 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd interview with Dr. Lev Dobriansky - Czechoslovakia’s spirit of freedom: Will it die?; Tape 4 For August 8 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interview with Dr. Lev Dobriansky - Unrest in Russia: Something we hear little about; Tape 5 For August 9 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - The Yoshida letter: Free China’s warning to Japan. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for August 12 - August 16, 1968; power_ts_0023; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 20)
      Tape 1, For August 12 (Monday) - Dr. Judd interview with Dr. Lev Dobriansky - Human Rights Or Wrongs?; Tape 2, For August 13 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - Red China’s Threat As Seen From Taiwan; Tape 3, For August 14 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd interviews J.F. Lewis - Russian Ploy In Berlin; Tape 4, For August 15 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - Russia’s Penetration Of Japan; Tape 5, For August 16 (Friday) - Dr. Judd interviews J.F. Lewis - Disarmament, Soviet Style. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for August 19 - August 23, 1968; power_ts_0024; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 21)
      Tape 1, For August 19 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - General Earle Wheeler And The Soviet Military Threat; Tape 2, For August 20 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd interviews John F. Lewis - Renewed Tensions In The Middle East; Tape 3, For August 21 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd interviews John F. Lewis - Soviet Spy Ships In The Americas; Tape 4, For August 22 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interviews John F. Lewis - New Kremlin Assault On Creative Artists; Tape 5, For August 23 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Red China’s Campaign In Burma. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for August 26 - August 30, 1968; power_ts_0025; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 21)
      Tape 1, For August 26 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - U.S. Commander’s Appraisal Of Latin Arms Needs; Tape 2, For August 27 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - Africa’s Chad: Strategic Ground For Russia; Tape 3, For August 28 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - ALSAM: New Missile Proposed For America’s Defense; Tape 4, For August 29 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - Illegality Of The Rhodesian Sanctions Raised; Tape 5, For August 30 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - General Shtemenko: The New Warsaw Pact Chief. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for September 2 - September 6, 1968; power_ts_0026; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 21)
      Tape 1, For September 2 (Monday) - Dr. Walter H. Judd interviews J.F. Lewis - Czechoslovakia’s Candle Of Freedom Snuffed Out; Tape 2, For September 3 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - A New British Attitude Toward Britain’s Asian Role; Tape 3, For September 4 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - Once Again The Red Menace Emerges In Indonesia; Tape 4, For September 5 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - Operation "Combat Fox" For South Korean Defenses; Tape 5, For September 6 - Dr. Judd - Red War In Portuguese Guinea: An Eyewitness Report. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for September 9 - September 13, 1968; power_ts_0027; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 21)
      Tape 1, For September 9 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - For The West, It Is Business As Usual Despite The Invasion Of Czechoslovakia; Tape 2, For September 10 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - The Message Of Communism Remains Unchanged; Tape 3, For September 11 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - Syria: Has Russia Gained Yet Another Satellite; Tape 4, For September 12 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - The U.S. Policy Of Abusing Our Friends, Whilst Making Friends With The Enemy; Tape 5, For September 13 (Friday) - Dr. Walter H. Judd interview with Mr. John F. Lewis - Ukrainian Unrest Behind The Czech Crisis. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for September 16 - September 20, 1968; power_ts_0028; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 21)
      Tape 1, For September 16 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - The Soviet Attitude Toward Rumania; Tape 2, For September 17 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - Lenin’s Message to Czechoslovakia; Tape 3, For September 18 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - Assassination of Ambassador Mein; Tape 4, For September 19 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - Latin American Bishops Dispute over Red Subversion; Tape 5, For September 20 (Friday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - Those Who Flee from Communism. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for September 23 - September 27, 1968; power_ts_0029; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 21)
      Tape 1, For September 23 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Vasily Kuznetsov, Moscow’s Hatchet-Man in Prague; Tape 2, For September 24 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - North Vietnam’s Support of Russian Oppression; Tape 3, For September 25 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - Television and the War in Vietnam; Tape 4, For September 26 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - Pyrrhic Victory May Be Mao’s Reward; Tape 5, For September 27 (Friday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - Russia Launches New Purge of Jews. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for September 30 - October 4, 1968; power_ts_0030; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 21)
      Tape 1, For September 20 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Soviet Threat to West Germany; Tape 2, For October 1 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - Soviets Mass Power Threat to West; Tape 3, For October 2 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - Extent of Mao’s "Cultural Revolution" Purges; Tape 4, For October 3 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - Sanctions on Rhodesia Punish African Neighbors; Tape 5, For October 4 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Yugoslavia Menaced by Warsaw Pact. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for October 7 - October 11, 1968; power_ts_0031; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 21)
      Tape 1, For October 7 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Peking Still Generates Agitation Abroad; Tape 2, For October 8 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd interview with Frank Johnson - Soviet Legalistic Threat to West Germany; Tape 3, For October 9 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - Forced Labor for Red China’s Students; Tape 4, For October 10 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - Free China’s Independence Day; Tape 5, For October 11 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Domino Theory Already in Practice. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for October 14 - October 18, 1968; power_ts_0032; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 21)
      Tape 1, For October 14 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Mexico’s Lesson in Communism; Tape 2, For October 15 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd interview with Frank Johnson - Soviet Targets: Rumania and Yugoslavia; Tape 3, For October 16 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - Aeroflot: Soviet Trojan Horse; Tape 4, For October 17 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - Eritrean Guerillas Suffer Setback; Tape 5, For October 18 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Hopeful Trends in Vietnam. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for October 21 - October 25, 1968; power_ts_0033; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 21)
      Tape 1, For October 21 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Red China’s New Aggression in India; Tape 2, For October 22 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - The Build-Up to Russia’s Newest Moves; Tape 2, For October 23 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - Indian Opposition to Red China Grows; Tape 2, For October 24 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - Jordan: Spark-Filled Powder Keg; Tape 5, For October 25 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Red China’s Consumer Goods Crisis. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for October 28 - November 1, 1968; power_ts_0034; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 21)
      Tape 1, For October 28 (Monday) - Dr. Judd interview with William K. Lambie - Plan to Bolster Internal Security; Tape 2, For October 29 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - The Dilemma of U.S. Isolationism; Tape 3, For October 30 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd interview with Dr. John H. Davis - Distribution of Palestine Arab Refugees; Tape 4, For October 31 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - More Military Coups in Latin America?; Tape 5, For November 1 (Friday) - Dr. Judd interview with Dr. John H. Davis - Plight of the Arab Refugees. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for November 4 - November 8, 1968; power_ts_0035; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 21)
      Tape 1, For November 4 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Latest Soviet Naval Developments; Tape 2, For November 5 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - Red China’s New Accomplishments; Tape 3, For November 6 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - Zambia: Newest Violator or African Freedom; Tape 4, For November 7 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interview with Dr. John H. Davis - How Reds Take Advantage of Arab Frustrations; Tape 5, For November 8 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Soviet Secret Police in Czechoslovakia. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for November 11 - November 15, 1968; power_ts_0036; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 21)
      Tape 1, For November 11 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Red Spy Penetration of NATO; Tape 2, For November 12 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - Algeria: Communism’s African Cuba; Tape 3, For November 13 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - Philby and NATO Spy Scandals; Tape 4, For November 14 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - Yugoslavia: Raw Nerves Exposed; Tape 5, For November 15 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Ancient China’s Techniques Used to Fight Mao. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for November 18 - November 22, 1968; power_ts_0037; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 21)
      Tape 1, For November 18 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - A U.S. Affront to Freedom; Tape 2, For November 19 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd interview with Harry E. Martens - Profiles of Arab Refugees; Tape 3, For November 20 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - Re-Alignment in the Kremlin; Tape 4, For November 21 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - Red Reverses in Burma; Tape 5, For November 22 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Czechoslovakia: Nation in Name Only. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for November 25 - November 29, 1968; power_ts_0038; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 21)
      Tape 1, For November 25 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Critical Image in Vietnam; Tape 2, For November 26 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - Cambodia urges U.S. stay in Asia; Tape 2, For November 27 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - Red Espionage Center in Mexico; Tape 4, For November 28 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - Red Tactical Dispute in Indonesia; Tape 5, For November 29 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Madame Mao’s Thoughts Muddy China Thinking. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for December 2 - December 6, 1968; power_ts_0039; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 21)
      Tape 1, For December 2 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - U.S. Bid for Castro’s Friendship; Tape 2, For December 3 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - Red China’s Base in Zanzibar; Tape 3, For December 4 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - NATO and the "Prague Coup"; Tape 4, For December 5 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - Biafra Backing from Red China; Tape 5, For December 6 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - France Wakes up to Algerian Menace. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for December 9 - December 13, 1968; power_ts_0040; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 22)
      Tape 1, For December 9 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Loss of Vietnam Subject of U.S. Debate; Tape 2, For December 10 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - Spain, U.S. Near Bases Accord; Tape 3, For December 11 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - Sabotage in Red Cuba; Tape 4, For December 12 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - Soviets Building Polaris Defense; Tape 5, For December 13 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - China Extends Isolation from West to Press. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for December 16 - December 20, 1968; power_ts_0041; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 22)